Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Harris County: South Side of Buffalo Bayou (SSBB)
    - Block 81
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 7th Floor, 1923-1926 (Box 172, Folder 25)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 7th Floor, 1927-1929 (Box 172, Folder 26)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 7th Floor, 1930-1942 (Box 172, Folder 27)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 8th Floor, 1923-1925 (Box 172, Folder 28)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 8th Floor, 1926-1927 (Box 172, Folder 29)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 8th Floor, 1928-1929 (Box 172, Folder 30)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 8th Floor, 1930-1955 (Box 172, Folder 31)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 9th Floor, 1923-1925 (Box 172, Folder 32)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 9th Floor, 1926-1927 (Box 172, Folder 33)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 9th Floor, 1928-1931 (Box 172, Folder 34)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 9th Floor, 1932-1941 (Box 172, Folder 35)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 10th Floor, 1923 (Box 172, Folder 36)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 10th Floor, 1925-1926 (Box 172, Folder 37)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 10th Floor, 1927-1929 (Box 172, Folder 38)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leases, 10th Floor, 1930-1941 (Box 172, Folder 39)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Leasehold and Fee (Box 173, Folder 1-3)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Tenant Leases, 1966-1992 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Floor Plans, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction Receipts, 1923 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building, 1939-1960 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Sale and Repurchase, 1939-1982 (Box 173, Folder 8-9)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Loan: Seven Hundred Main, Inc., 1939 (Box 173, Folder 10-11)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1966 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1966 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1967 (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1967 (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1967 (Box 173, Folder 16)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Construction, 1967 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1968 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1969 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1970 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1971 (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1972 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1976-1977 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1978-1979 (Box 174, Folder 12-14)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 15-16)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1980-1982 (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; R/R, 1983-1990 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Carrier A/C Service + Invoices, 1972-1977 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Southern Elevator Corp., 1972-1994 (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Window Cleaning, 1980-1992 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; JWP Gowen Inc. A/C Services, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; A-1 Reporting Service, Inc., 1991 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Rent, 1983-1992 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Cushman + Wakefield, 1991-1993 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Tenant Notice to Vacate, 1972 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; J Ray Farley Bankruptcy, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 10)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; UPI Bankruptcy, 1991-1993 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Benton Musselwhite Bankruptcy, 1973-1993 (Box 175, Folder 12)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; City of Houston, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 13)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Invoices, 1993-1995 (Box 175, Folder 14)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos Project, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 15)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 175, Folder 16)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 17)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos Projects, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 18)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos Projects, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 19)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos Projects, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 20)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Post Job Submittals, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 21)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Post Job Submittals, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 22)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Agreement w/ CST Environmental, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 23)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Hazardous Waste Manifests, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 24)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Application for Payment, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 25)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Asbestos Project, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 26)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Notes + Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 27)
      - Agreement w/ ERC, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 28)
      - Original Bids from Four Companies, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 29)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Ledgers, 1961-1991 (Box 175, Folder 30)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; National Bank of Commerce, Complete Period of Ownership, 1948 (Box 176, Folder 1-4)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; National Bank of Commerce, Complete Period of Ownership, 1948-1961 (Box 176, Folder 5)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; National Bank of Commerce, Complete Period of Ownership, 1948-1961 (Box 177, Folder 1-3)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; Transfer Ledger, 1965-1987 (Box 177, Folder 4-5)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; Transfer Ledger, 1965-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1-2)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; Ledger, 1965-1977 (Box 178, Folder 3-5)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; Transfer Ledger, 1978-1988 (Box 179, Folder 1-2)
        - Bankers Mortgage Building; Transfer Ledger, 1988-1991 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1895-1914 (Box 175, Folder 31)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1915-1920 (Box 175, Folder 32)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1922 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1922-1939 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1939-1960 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1962-1968 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Bankers Mortgage Building; Abstracts of Title, 1975-1978 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Clay Building; Dunlay-Clay Building Agreement, 1893 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Clay Building; Building Exam, 1949 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Clay and Helberg Buildings; Property Lines, 1949 (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Goggan Building; Lobby Specs., 1908 (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Goggan Building; Construction Contracts, 1908-1909 (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Goggan Building; Construction Receipts, 1908-1910 (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Goggan Building; The Texas Co. Lease, 1909 (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Goggan Building; Southern Loan and Investment Co. to Texas Trust Co., 1909 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Goggan Building; J.W. Carter Music Co. Lease, 1909-1917 (Box 180, Folder 14)
      - Goggan Building; Party Wall Agreement, 1912-1916 (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - Goggan Building; Notes, 1914-1916 (Box 180, Folder 16)
      - Goggan Building; Southern Loan and Investment Co. to A.L. Bowers, 1916 (Box 180, Folder 17)
      - Goggan Building; A.L. Bowers 99 year Lease to JHJ, 1916 (Box 180, Folder 18)
      - Goggan Building; Document Receipts, 1916-1929 (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - Goggan Building; Mason Building Co. to Goggan Building Co., 1917 (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Goggan Building; Thos. Goggan + Bro. Lease, 1917-1923 (Box 180, Folder 21)
      - Goggan Building; Tax Receipts, 1918 (Box 180, Folder 22)
      - Goggan Building; Insurance, 1918-1919 (Box 180, Folder 23)
      - Goggan Building; Notes, 1912 (Box 180, Folder 24)
      - Goggan Building; Continental Trust Co. To Edgewood Realty Co., 1915 (Box 180, Folder 25)
      - Goggan Building; Hermann Estate Note, 1917 (Box 180, Folder 26)
      - Goggan Building; Notes, 1922 (Box 180, Folder 27)
      - Goggan Building; Humble Oil Lease, 1921 (Box 180, Folder 28)
      - Goggan Building; Blue Prints, 1909 (Box 180, Folder 29)
      - Goggan Building Property; Abstract, 1897-1909 (Box 180, Folder 30)
      - Goggan Building Property; Repsdorph Documents, 1895-1906 (Box 180, Folder 31)
      - Goggan Building Property; M. Scholibo to D.R. Beatty, 1897-1904 (Box 180, Folder 32)
      - Goggan Building Property; Paving Certificate, 1900 (Box 180, Folder 33)
      - Goggan Building Property; D.R. Beatty to J. Kirby, 1905 (Box 180, Folder 34)
      - Goggan Building Property; Title Opinion, 1905 (Box 180, Folder 35)
      - Goggan Building Property; Quit-Claim Deed to John Kirby, 1906 (Box 180, Folder 36)
      - Goggan Building Property; J. Kirby to W. Chew + H. Levy, 1906 (Box 180, Folder 37)
      - Goggan Building Property; Abstract, 1912-1914 (Box 180, Folder 38)
      - Goggan-Woolworth Building Ledgers, 1932-1934 (Box 180, Folder 39)
        - Goggan-Woolworth Buildings; Cash Record, 1932-1934 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Gulf Building; Construction, 1927-1931 (Box 180, Folder 40)
      - Gulf Building; Operating Costs, 1930-1933 (Box 180, Folder 41)
      - Gulf Building; Loans, 1928-1933 (Box 180, Folder 42)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1929 (Box 180, Folder 43)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1929 (Box 180, Folder 44)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1929 (Box 180, Folder 45)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1929 (Box 180, Folder 46)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1929 (Box 180, Folder 47)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1930 (Box 180, Folder 48)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1931-1932 (Box 180, Folder 49)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1933 (Box 180, Folder 50)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, Sakowitz Brothers, 1934 (Box 180, Folder 51)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, 1934-1937 (Box 180, Folder 52)
      - Gulf Building; Leases, Palais Royal, 1953 (Box 180, Folder 53)
      - Gulf Building; Descriptions, 1929-1930 (Box 180, Folder 54)
      - Gulf Building; Income Statement, 1930 (Box 180, Folder 55)
      - Gulf Building, 1930-1955 (Box 180, Folder 56)
      - Gulf Building, 1952-1959 (Box 180, Folder 57)
      - Appraisal, 1954 (Box 180, Folder 58)
      - Gulf Building; Alteration and Additions, 1958-1959 (Box 180, Folder 59)
      - Exterior Rehabilitation, 1976 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Various Documents, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Gulf Building Construction, 1927-132 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Building Lines, 1946-1950 (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Title Exams, 1948 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Captrav Realty Co. to JHJ, 1948 (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - Gulf Building Annex; JHJ to Bristol Realty Co., 1948 (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Bristol Realty Co. to The National Bank of Commerce, 1948 (Box 181, Folder 8)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Notes, 1948-1962 (Box 181, Folder 9)
      - Gulf Building Additon, 1950-1951 (Box 181, Folder 10)
      - Gulf Building Additon, 1950-1952 (Box 181, Folder 11)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Notes, 1951 (Box 181, Folder 12)
      - Gulf Building Annex; Appraisal, 1952 (Box 181, Folder 13)
      - Gulf Building Property; E+M Noble to C.M. Allen, 1861 (Box 181, Folder 14)
      - Gulf Building Property; Planters Mutual Inc. Co. Release to C. Allen, 1872 (Box 181, Folder 15)
      - Gulf Building Property; C.M. Allen to T.P. Converse, 1886-1905 (Box 181, Folder 16)
      - Gulf Building Property; Paving Certificate, 1900 (Box 181, Folder 17)
      - Gulf Building Property; T.P. Converse Will, 1900 (Box 181, Folder 18)
      - Gulf Building Property; T.P. Converse to J.Kirby, 1902 (Box 181, Folder 19)
      - Gulf Building Property; Title Exams, 1905 (Box 181, Folder 20)
      - Gulf Building Property; Survey, 1905 (Box 181, Folder 21)
      - Gulf Building Property; Quit-Claim Deeds to John Kirby, 1905 (Box 181, Folder 22)
      - Gulf Building Property; J. Converse Estate to T.P. Converse, 1905 (Box 181, Folder 23)
      - Gulf Building Property; Notes, 1905-1910 (Box 181, Folder 24)
      - Gulf Building Property; John Kirby to W. Chew + H. Levy, 1906 (Box 181, Folder 25)
      - Gulf Building Property; Bills + Receipts, 1906-1907 (Box 181, Folder 26)
      - Gulf Building Property; JHJ to H. Masterson (9/10 Interest), 1907 (Box 181, Folder 27)
      - Gulf Building Property; Tax Receipts, 1907-1911 (Box 181, Folder 28)
      - Gulf Building Property; JHJ to Texas Trust Co., 1909 (Box 181, Folder 29)
      - Gulf Building Property; Notes, 1913 (Box 181, Folder 30)
      - Gulf Building Property; Warranty Deeds, 1913 (Box 181, Folder 31)
      - Gulf Building Property; Document Receipts, 1913-1922 (Box 181, Folder 32)
      - Gulf Building Property; Notes, 1914-1916 (Box 181, Folder 33)
      - Gulf Building Property; Bankers Trust Co. to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1916 (Box 181, Folder 34)
      - Gulf Building Property; Notes, 1917-1921 (Box 181, Folder 35)
      - Gulf Building Property; Abstracts, 1907-1918 (Box 181, Folder 36)
      - Helberg Building; Notes, 1893-1916 (Box 181, Folder 37)
      - Helberg Building; A. Dunlay to C. Bender, 1903 (Box 181, Folder 38)
      - Helberg Building; Bender Agreement with Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1911 (Box 181, Folder 39)
      - Helberg Building; Title Exam, 1911 (Box 181, Folder 40)
      - Helberg Building; Documents Receipts, 1911-1924 (Box 181, Folder 41)
      - Helberg Building; Tax Receipts, 1911-1924 (Box 181, Folder 42)
      - Helberg Building; Lot 11 AKA Texan Theatre, 1911-1972 (Box 181, Folder 43)
      - Helberg Building; Lot 11 AKA Texan Theatre, 1911-1972 (Box 181, Folder 44)
      - Helberg Building; Leases, 1918-1932 (Box 181, Folder 45)
      - Helberg Building; Alterations (RIES Annex), 1922 (Box 181, Folder 46)
      - Helberg Building; Henke Notes, 1924-1925 (Box 181, Folder 47)
      - Helberg Building; Genora Restaurant Fire, 1924-1925 (Box 181, Folder 48)
      - Helberg Building; Sprinkler System, 1927 (Box 181, Folder 49)
      - Helberg Building; Notes, 1942 (Box 181, Folder 50)
      - Hotel Proposal, 1909 (Box 181, Folder 51)
      - Hudson Building; Title Exam, 1912 (Box 181, Folder 52)
      - Hudson Building; J.O. Ross Warranty Deed to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1912 (Box 181, Folder 53)
      - Hudson Building; Notes, 1912 (Box 181, Folder 54)
      - Hudson Building; Lease, 1915 (Box 181, Folder 55)
      - Hudson Building; Bankers Trust Co. to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1916 (Box 181, Folder 56)
      - Hudson Building; Notes, 1916 (Box 181, Folder 57)
      - Hudson Building; Notes, 1921-1928 (Box 181, Folder 58)
      - Hudson Building; Fire Escape, 1924 (Box 181, Folder 59)
      - Hudson Building; Goggan Brothers Lease, 1926 (Box 181, Folder 60)
      - Hudson Building; Map, 1928 (Box 181, Folder 61)
      - Hudson Building; Abstract Receipt, 1929 (Box 181, Folder 62)
      - Levy Building; Leases, 1916-1919 (Box 181, Folder 63)
      - Levy Building; Taxes and Income, 1916-1920 (Box 181, Folder 64)
      - Levy Building; Proposals, 1919-1920 (Box 181, Folder 65)
      - Levy Building; Leases, 1920 (Box 181, Folder 66)
      - Levy Building; Leases, 1920 (Box 181, Folder 67)
      - Levy Building; Leases, National Shirt Shops, 1920 (Box 181, Folder 68)
      - Levy Building; McCardell and Saver Controversy, 1920-1921 (Box 181, Folder 69)
      - Levy Building; Leases, 1921 (Box 181, Folder 70)
      - Levy Building; Leases, 1921-1922 (Box 181, Folder 71)
      - Levy Building; Wall Agreement, 1921 (Box 181, Folder 72)
      - Levy Building; Land Lease, 1921 (Box 181, Folder 73)
      - Levy Building; Proposals, 1921 (Box 181, Folder 74)
      - Levy Building; Proposals, 1922 (Box 181, Folder 75)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Lease- A.B. Clow, 1911-1912 (Box 181, Folder 76)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Proposals, 1912 (Box 181, Folder 77)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Lease- J. Pearce, 1912-1918 (Box 181, Folder 78)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Organ, 1913 (Box 181, Folder 79)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Elevator Agreement with Woolworth Building, 1913 (Box 181, Folder 80)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Sub-Lease- J.Pearce to J. Davis, 1914-1916 (Box 181, Folder 81)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Inventory, 1916 (Box 181, Folder 82)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Lease- Queen Theatre Co. (Renamed "The Liberty"), 1916-1917 (Box 181, Folder 83)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Sublease- Queen Theatre Co. to E. Johnston, 1917-198 (Box 181, Folder 84)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Lease- Southern Enterprises, Inc., 1920-1921 (Box 181, Folder 85)
      - Pearce's Theatre; Additional Floors, 1925 (Box 181, Folder 86)
      - Roxford Apartments; Paving Certificate, 1900 (Box 181, Folder 87)
      - Roxford Apartments; Notes, 1906-1912 (Box 181, Folder 88)
      - Roxford Apartments; Title Exam, 1908 (Box 181, Folder 89)
      - Roxford Apartments; D.R. Beatty to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1908-1909 (Box 181, Folder 90)
      - Roxford Apartments; Tax Receipts, 1909-1912 (Box 181, Folder 91)
      - Roxford Apartments; Southern Loan and Investment Co. to Edgewood Realty, 1911 (Box 181, Folder 92)
      - Roxford Apartments; Document Receipts, 1912-1934 (Box 181, Folder 93)
      - Roxford Apartments; Notes, 1913-1923 (Box 181, Folder 94)
      - Roxford Apartments; Leases, 1915-1921 (Box 181, Folder 95)
      - Roxford Apartments; Mason Building Co. to Bankers Trust Co., 1916 (Box 181, Folder 96)
      - Roxford Apartments; Bankers Trust Co. to Mason Building Co., 1917 (Box 181, Folder 97)
      - Roxford Apartments; Leases, 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 98)
      - Roxford Apartments; Fire Escape, 1924 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Roxford Apartments; Leases, 1924-1926 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Roxford Apartments; Leases, 1927-1939 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Roxford Apartments; Gulf Building Corp. Lease to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1931 (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Roxford Apartments; Financing, 1931 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Abstract of Title, Lot 2, 1916 (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Loan- Lots 4, 9, 10 + 11, 1950-1965 (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Rusk Hotel; Pearce's Theatre Property, Affidavit, 1905 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - Rusk Hotel; Pearce's Theatre, Notes, 1907-1914 (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - Rusk Hotel; Pearce's Theatre, Notes, 1916-1921 (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - Rusk Hotel; Leases, 1917-1919 (Box 182, Folder 11)
      - Rusk Hotel; Fire Escape, 1924 (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - Various Lots and Buildings, 1907-1949 (Box 182, Folder 13)
      - Woolworth Building; Notes, 1907-1922 (Box 182, Folder 14)
      - Woolworth Building; JHJ to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1910 (Box 182, Folder 15)
      - Woolworth Building; Construction Contract, 1912 (Box 182, Folder 16)
      - Woolworth Building; Party Wall Agreement, 1916 (Box 182, Folder 17)
      - Woolworth Building and Goggan Buildings; Connection Estimate, 1923 (Box 182, Folder 18)
      - Woolworth Building; Pearce's Theatre Heating, 1919 (Box 182, Folder 19)
      - Woolworth Building; Pearce's Theatre Additional Floors, 1925 (Box 182, Folder 20)
      - Woolworth Building Property, Quit-claim Deed to John Kirby, 1905-1906 (Box 182, Folder 21)
      - Woolworth Building Property, Abstracts, 1906-1916 (Box 182, Folder 22)
      - Abstract of Title, Lots 1, 2, 3, 11, 12, 1917 (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Block 82
      - Black Bros. Building, 1954 (Box 182, Folder 24)
      - Bristol Hotel; Lease, 1895 (Box 182, Folder 25)
      - Bristol Hotel; Rogers Lease, 1906 (Box 182, Folder 26)
      - Bristol Hotel; JHJ to L. Jones, 1907 (Box 182, Folder 27)
      - Bristol Hotel; F.A. Hervey Agreements, 1907 (Box 182, Folder 28)
      - Bristol Hotel; Tax Receipts, 1907-1911 (Box 182, Folder 29)
      - Bristol Hotel; Inventory, 1907-1919 (Box 182, Folder 30)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, 1907-1922 (Box 182, Folder 31)
      - Bristol Hotel; Specifications, 1908 (Box 182, Folder 32)
      - Bristol Hotel; F.A. Hervey Agreements, 1908 (Box 182, Folder 33)
      - Bristol Hotel; Sanguinet and STAATS Receipts, 1908-1909 (Box 182, Folder 34)
      - Bristol Hotel; H.L. Stevens Co. Receipts + Contracts, 1908-1909 (Box 182, Folder 35)
      - Bristol Hotel; Receipts and Invoices, Construction, 1908-1911 (Box 182, Folder 36)
      - Bristol Hotel; Proposals, 1908-1914 (Box 182, Folder 37)
      - Bristol Hotel; Change Order, JHJ, 1909 (Box 182, Folder 38)
      - Bristol Hotel; Millwork, 1909 (Box 182, Folder 39)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones note, $25,000, 1909 (Box 182, Folder 40)
      - Bristol Hotel; JHJ to Southern Loan and Investment Co., 1909 (Box 182, Folder 41)
      - Bristol Hotel; Southern Loan and Investment Co. to L. Johns, 1909 (Box 182, Folder 42)
      - Bristol Hotel; F.A. Hervey Agreements, 1909-1919 (Box 182, Folder 43)
      - Bristol Hotel; American Construction Co. Receipts and Extra Work Orders, 1909-1910 (Box 182, Folder 44)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones- House Agreements, 1910 (Box 182, Folder 45)
      - Bristol Hotel; Financial Statements, 1913-1925 (Box 182, Folder 46)
      - Bristol Hotel; Insurance, 1913-1926 (Box 182, Folder 47)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $75,000, 1914 (Box 182, Folder 48)
      - Bristol Hotel; F.A. Hervey Lease, 1915-1918 (Box 182, Folder 49)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $75,000, 1916 (Box 182, Folder 50)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $80,000, 1916-1921 (Box 182, Folder 51)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $125,000, 1916-1925 (Box 182, Folder 52)
      - Bristol Hotel Receipts, 1916-1931 (Box 182, Folder 53)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $75,000, 1917-1921 (Box 182, Folder 54)
      - Bristol Hotel Repair Receipts, 1919 (Box 182, Folder 55)
      - Bristol Hotel Linens, 1919 (Box 182, Folder 56)
      - Bristol Hotel; Furniture Sale, 1919 (Box 182, Folder 57)
      - Bristol Hotel; G. Hall Lease, 1919-1929 (Box 182, Folder 58)
      - Bristol Hotel; Leases, 1919-1926 (Box 182, Folder 59)
      - Bristol Hotel; Fire Escapes, 1920-1924 (Box 182, Folder 60)
      - Plot Maps, 1923-1945 (Box 182, Folder 61)
      - Bristol Hotel; Underpin Walls, 1924 (Box 182, Folder 62)
      - Bristol Hotel; BPOE Building Proposal, 1926 (Box 182, Folder 63)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $125,000, 1926-1931 (Box 182, Folder 64)
      - Bristol Hotel; Insurance, 1927-1932 (Box 182, Folder 65)
      - Bristol Hotel; S.W. Bell Telephone, 1928 (Box 182, Folder 66)
      - Bristol Hotel; JM Bowman Lease, 1929-1930 (Box 182, Folder 67)
      - Bristol Hotel; Inventory, 1929-1935 (Box 182, Folder 68)
      - Bristol Hotel; Thompson and Velin, Lease, 1931 (Box 182, Folder 69)
      - Bristol Hotel; Light and power, 1931 (Box 182, Folder 70)
      - Bristol Hotel; Robb Lease, 1932-1936 (Box 182, Folder 71)
      - Bristol Hotel; L. Jones Note, $125,000, 1932-1936 (Box 182, Folder 72)
      - Bristol Hotel; Insurance, 1933 (Box 182, Folder 73)
      - Bristol Hotel; Insurance, 1934-1935 (Box 182, Folder 74)